{
    "quizDetails": [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "title": "JavaQuiz"
        },
        {
            "id": 1,
            "title": "JavascriptQuiz"
        }
    ],
    "questionsQ1": [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "prompt": "How do you declare an ArrayList of type Integer named 'values?' ",
            "choices": [
                "ArrayList values = new ArrayList<Integer>();",
                "ArrayList values = new ArrayList<int>();",
                "ArrayList values = new ArrayList<Integer>;",
                "ArrayList values = new ArrayList<int>;"
            ],
            "correctChoice": 0,
            "explanation": "Sorry you were wrong, the correct answer is A. ArrayList values = new ArrayList<Integer>(). ArrayLists cannot be composed of primitive data types, and since int is a primative type, you must use the wrapper class version of int, Integer. Also, ArrayList is a class, which is why is must include parenthases at the end."
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "type": "narrative",
            "prompt": "What is the sum of 1 + 1?",
            "choices": [
                "2",
                "-2",
                "11",
                "5"
            ],
            "correctChoice": 2,
            "explanation": "Sorry you were wrong, the correct answer is 2. Learn math"
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "prompt": "What method has the same name as the class and no return type?",
            "choices": [
                "compare To method",
                "constructor method",
                "equals method",
                "round method"
            ],
            "correctChoice": 1,
            "explanation": "Sorry you were wrong, the correct answer is B. constructor method. Constructor methods are unique methods that have the same name as the class and no return type. The other methods listed are just built-in java methods."
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "type": "image",
            "prompt": "Which image shows a recursive method that would have a StackOverFlowError?",
            "choices": [
                "wrong",
                "right"
            ],
            "correctChoice": 1,
            "explanation": "Sorry you were wrong, the correct answer is B. The second recursive call does not have a terminal condition, and so it will loop infinitely leading to a StackOverFlowError."
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "prompt": "When dealing with file handling, what must you first import?",
            "choices": [
                "java.io.File",
                "java.io.file",
                "java.util.File",
                "java.util.file"
            ],
            "correctChoice": 0,
            "explanation": "Sorry you were wrong, the correct answer is A.java.io.File. The File class is apart of the java.io package, and File must start with an uppercase as the language is case-sensitive. "
        }
    ],
    "questionsQ2": [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "prompt": "Which choice shows the correct syntax for defining a function named value with paramaters x and y using arrow syntax?",
            "choices": [
                "function value (x,y) => { }",
                "function value = (x,y) => { }",
                "let value = x,y => { }",
                "let value = (x,y) => { }"
            ],
            "correctChoice": 4,
            "explanation": "Sorry you were wrong, the correct answer is D. let value = (x,y) => { }. For arrow syntax you must invoke it using a variable. "
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "type": "narrative",
            "prompt": "What is the sum of 1 + 1?",
            "choices": [
                "2",
                "-2",
                "11",
                "5"
            ],
            "correctChoice": 0,
            "explanation": "Sorry you were wrong, the correct answer is"
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "prompt": "What is the correct keyword for declaring a variable with a block scope?",
            "choices": [
                "var",
                "const",
                "let",
                "int"
            ],
            "correctChoice": 2,
            "explanation": "Sorry you were wrong, the correct answer is C. let.  In Javascript you can define a variable with both the keywords 'let' and 'var', but 'var' has a lexical scope while 'let' has a block scope."
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "type": "Which image shows the ",
            "prompt": "What is the sum of 1 + 1?",
            "choices": [
                "2",
                "-2"
            ],
            "correctChoice": 0,
            "explanation": "Sorry you were wrong, the correct answer is"
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "type": "multipleChoice",
            "prompt": "What is the correct syntax for a string literal?",
            "choices": [
                "'${text}'",
                "`${text}`",
                "/${text}/",
                "${text}"
            ],
            "correctChoice": 1,
            "explanation": "Sorry you were wrong, the correct answer is B. `${text}`."
        }
    ]
}
